#### Contact

ugwunzetobenna@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tobennaugwunze-1b325b203 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Social Media Content Strategy Brand Management

### Certifications

Fundamentals of Digital Marketing Copywriting for Social Media

# Tobenna Ugwunze

Seasoned Creative Storyteller and Voiceover artist.

Federal Capital Territory, Nigeria

## Summary

Tobenna Ugwunze is a talented and seasoned creative storyteller and voice over artist. In a book, marketing campaign, earned media campaign, or even on your website and marketing materials, he would creatively bring your unique voice to life.

As a passionate brand communicator, active within the writing community for almost 5 years, he has worked with individuals and brands in B2B marketing agencies, luxury real estate, e-commerce, hospitality, aviation, financial services, food brands, and everything else in between.

His expertise in curating fun and engaging copies, well-researched PR articles, exciting radio, TVC and film scripts is guaranteed to result in clear brand communication and increased conversation and engagement with the target audience.

His abilities are not limited to the pen, keypad or microphone, but as he will always say, a story of a hundred pages begins with one word.

## Experience

The Rage Group Creative Storyteller April 2021 - Present (2 years 1 month) Abuja, Federal Capital Territory, Nigeria

The Driven Grit Agency
Content Developer
March 2020 - Present (3 years 2 months)

Garden of Grace Director Of Media Services January 2020 - March 2020 (3 months) Nigeria Leading the subgroups of the media team responsible for video and picture coverage of meetings and programmes, launching social media campaigns and development of contents.

## Education

Nnamdi Azikiwe University

Coorperative Economics and Management · (2011 - 2015)